♪I don't want to be free♪
♪ لا أريد أن أكون حراً ♪
=I Don't Want To Fall in Love with Human=
= لا أريد الوقوع في حب الإنسان =
Zeyi, let me help you.
Zeyi ، دعني أساعدك.
Miaomiao, are you tired?
مياومياو ، هل أنت متعب؟
Why not you go and take a rest?
لماذا لا تذهب وتأخذ قسطا من الراحة؟
Momo, I've been looking for you.
مومو ، كنت أبحث عنك.
You're looking for me?
هل تبحث عني؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Bai Qing,
باي تشينغ ،
is Zeyi really into taking a bath?
هل تحب زيي الاستحمام حقًا؟
Of course. If you clean the pool,
بالطبع.  إذا قمت بتنظيف المسبح ،
Zeyi will think of you whenever he's taking a bath.
سوف يفكر Zeyi فيك عندما يستحم.
Okay.
تمام.
Here, change to some clean water.
هنا ، قم بالتغيير إلى بعض المياه النظيفة.
Where are Uncle Hai and Momo?
أين العم هاي ومومو؟
Momo is sick. Uncle Hai's sending her home.
مومو مريض.  يرسل العم هاي منزلها.
Uncle Hai, you're leaving?
العم هاي ، هل سترحل؟
I wonder why Momo is
أتساءل لماذا مومو
suddenly having an allergy.
فجأة تعاني من الحساسية.
I need to quickly bring her to a doctor.
أحتاج إلى إحضارها بسرعة إلى الطبيب.
Is she okay?
هل هي بخير؟
Miaomiao, don't you dislike Momo?
مياومياو ، ألا تكره مومو؟
Who said that?
من قال هذا؟
She's fine.
انها بخير.
She'll be fine after checking by the doctor in the hospital.
ستكون بخير بعد فحصها من قبل الطبيب في المستشفى.
Miaomiao, do you like to eat Qing Bu Liang?
مياومياو ، هل تحب أكل تشينغ بو ليانغ؟
Zeyi likes to eat it.
زيي يحب أكله.
Miaomiao, I kept this for you.
Miaomiao ، لقد احتفظت بهذا من أجلك.
Thank you. But I don't like to eat it.
شكرًا لك.  لكني لا أحب أكله.
Are you not welcoming Bai Qing?
هل أنت غير مرحب بباي تشينغ؟
Not just that.
ليس ذلك فحسب.
Do you know what she has done?
هل تعلم ماذا فعلت؟
What has she done?
ماذا فعلت؟
She wanted to acquire the beach. My homestay...
أرادت الحصول على الشاطئ.  إقامتي ...
My homestay was the last that didn't sign the agreement.
كانت إقامتي في المنزل هي آخر من لم يوقع الاتفاقية.
They've been trying to chase me away.
لقد كانوا يحاولون مطاردتي بعيدًا.
Miaomiao, are you thinking too much?
مياومياو ، هل تفكر كثيرا؟
We're fish. We're not that bad.
نحن نصطاد.  نحن لسنا بهذا السوء.
You're fish.
أنت سمكة.
You either stay here for nothing
إما أن تبقى هنا من أجل لا شيء
or you try to acquire my homestay.
أو تحاول الحصول على مسكني.
You even pretend to look weak.
حتى أنك تتظاهر بأنك تبدو ضعيفًا.
Miaomiao.
مياومياو.
Zeyi.
زي.
Gu Zeyi.
قو زيي.
What's wrong with him?
ماذا حل به؟
Zeyi must have fainted because
يجب أن يكون زيي قد أغمي عليه بسبب
he doesn't have the sea pearl.
ليس لديه لؤلؤة البحر.
Ze'er.
جداً.
Bai Qing is not an outsider.
باي تشينغ ليس دخيلاً.
Zeyi's sea pearl was swallowed by Miaomiao.
ابتلع مياومياو لؤلؤة البحر لزيي.
His sea pearl was swallowed by Miaomiao?
لقد ابتلع مياومياو لؤلؤته البحرية؟
Maybe I have a solution.
ربما لدي حل.
There's nothing recorded on the Encyclopedia.
لا يوجد شيء مسجل في الموسوعة.
What solution do you have?
ما الحل الذي لديك؟
I'll check the Encyclopedia again.
سوف أتحقق من الموسوعة مرة أخرى.
Miaomiao, take care of Zeyi.
Miaomiao ، اعتني Zeyi.
If I knew it'd be this dangerous,
إذا علمت أن الأمر سيكون بهذا الخطورة ،
I wouldn't have let Zeyi come onshore.
لم أكن لأدع زيي يأتي إلى الشاطئ.
It's just the matter of succeeding the throne.
إنها فقط مسألة خلافة العرش.
I'm young. I can do that.
انا شاب.  أستطيع فعل ذلك.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm sprinkling salt.
أنا أرش الملح.
Why are you sprinkling salt?
لماذا ترش الملح؟
We're fish that live in the sea.
نحن أسماك نعيش في البحر.
Maybe when the water is salty,
ربما عندما يكون الماء مالحًا ،
Zeyi will wake up.
سوف تستيقظ زيي.
This is sea water.
هذه مياه بحر.
Sea water?
مياه البحر؟
Gu Zeyi.
قو زيي.
You're awake.
انت مستيقظ.
I'm thirsty.
عطشان.
It's so salty.
إنه مالح جدا.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
You better get up first.
من الأفضل أن تستيقظ أولاً.
Otherwise, you'll become salted fish.
خلاف ذلك ، سوف تصبح سمكة مملحة.
Zesan.
زيسان.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Where did you get this?
من اين حصلت على هذا؟
This is the only thing my father left to me,
هذا هو الشيء الوحيد الذي تركه لي والدي ،
but I think you need it more than me.
لكني أعتقد أنك بحاجة إليها أكثر مني.
So I'm giving it to you.
لذلك أنا أعطيها لك.
You're giving it to me?
أنت تعطيه لي؟
Are you sure that you're giving it to me?
هل أنت متأكد أنك ستعطيها لي؟
Two pages? There's one page short.
صفحتين؟  هناك صفحة واحدة قصيرة.
But that's all I have.
لكن هذا كل ما لدي.
No worries.
لا تقلق.
I'm just curious what's written on the other page.
أشعر بالفضول فقط لما هو مكتوب في الصفحة الأخرى.
You can retrieve the sea pearl when your loved one kisses you.
يمكنك استرداد لؤلؤة البحر عندما يقبلك أحد أفراد أسرتك.
Good news for Zeyi.
بشرى سارة لزيي.
Bai Qing, thank you so much.
باي تشينغ ، شكرا جزيلا لك.
♪The sign of the sea wind blown by♪
علامة ريح البحر التي تهب بها ♪
♪The footprint on the beach♪
البصمة على الشاطئ
♪You and I in the rain♪
♪ أنت وأنا في المطر ♪
♪Are so poetic♪
♪ هل شعرية جدا ♪
♪Regarding the future♪
بخصوص المستقبل
♪That we painted♪
♪ الذي رسمناه ♪
♪Every word we say♪
♪ كل كلمة نقولها ♪
♪Is surreal♪
♪ هل سريالية